Today's temperature will reach
32 degrees Celsius.
The first day of summer heat is expected.
In areas including Yokohama Saitama
and Chiba,
it's expected to be
5 to 8 degrees higher than usual.
If observed, April 11th's summer heat
would be the earliest on record.
This unusual April heat is
expected to reach mid-August levels.
Hey, are you okay?
Wanna come to my place?
Is that… okay?
RIHITO TATSUNO
KOINOBA HOT SPRINGS
Mr. Mori?
What's wrong? It's so late.
Is tomato juice okay for you, Mr. Mori?
I'm sorry for the trouble.
I just couldn't sleep.
You should go to bed early.
Tomorrow's your entrance ceremony.
I know, but I'm just nervous.
You don't need to be nervous.
If anything happens at school,
I'll come running right away.
You're so dramatic, Mr. Mori.
As long as I live,
I've made a promise to protect Rihito.
Thank you, Mr. Mori.
Oh, sorry for interrupting your work.
No, it's fine.
Good night, Rihito.
Good night, Mr. Mori.
See you, Mr. Mori.
How innocent he is…
Such a pure and rich aroma
wafts through the air.
I can't do this.
Geez…
Ba ba ba ba ba ba vampire
Ranmaru Mori, Ranmaru Mori
Ranmaru Mori, 450 years old
Ranmaru Mori, Vampire
Long ago, I was beloved by
The great Lord Oda Nobunaga
In the end, a sad farewell
Only I remained alive
Lord Nobunaga!
Vampires are immortal
Cursing this world and myself
I've spent hundreds of years in despair
No matter how many people's blood I drink
My thirst and hunger are never satisfied
Humans are just food
Eventually hunted by vampire hunters
Ready to die at that moment
Then I met him, a boy like an angel
His name is Rihito Tatsuno
Ranmaru Mori, Ranmaru Mori
Ranmaru Mori, 450 years old
Ranmaru Mori, Vampire
Clear eyes, pure heart
Elastic skin, innocent reactions
The scent of blood, everything is perfect
A once in a century treasure
I want Rihito's blood
Rihito's blood, Rihito's blood
The most delicious meal
Should be savored at its finest
The perfect state is
An 18-year-old virgin, nothing better
An 18-year-old virgin
Just three more years
Of filling my hunger
With criminals' disgusting blood
To savor Rihito the ultimate feast
In his perfect state
An 18 year old virgin
Who are you!?
I am a vampire.
A vampire?
Mori Ranmaru, 450 years old
- A cross.
- That won't work on me.
Mori Ranmaru, Mori Ranmaru the Vampire
Disgusting.
No Rihito, no life
It's so moving that
Rihito is now a high school student.
We're getting older too, aren't we?
Who's in high school?
It's me, Grandpa.
High school means youth,
and youth means love!
Grandpa, your buttons
are misaligned again.
Misaligned buttons happen all the time.
Buttons and love too.
Huh? Love?
Love is…
not necessary for high school students.
Love is nonsense!
- Good morning, Mr. Mori.
- Good morning.
It's rare to see you up this early,
Ran-chan.
That's right. Handsome men like you
must avoid sunburn.
Today is Rihito's entrance ceremony.
You woke up early just for me?
Of course.
Who are you again?
I'm Ranmaru Mori.
Oh? How old are you?
I'm 450 years old. Physically 25, though.
Oh my, that's quite a long life!
Could you be
the Grim Reaper coming for me?
No, I'm a vampire.
A vampire.
Ran-chan, your jokes always make me laugh!
Here, Ran-chan. Tomato juice.
Thank you.
It doesn't have nutrients
but it's best for quenching thirst.
Your vampire persona is really consistent.
Oh, Rihito! Hurry up or you'll be late!
Oh, you're right. I need to go.
I'm off. Have a good day.
Rihito, wait! I still need to talk.
Rihito, Rihito!
Hot!
Damn! This sun…
ENTRANCE CEREMONY
Alright, that's all for today.
Mr. Mori.
No running in the hallway.
Rihito.
What's wrong? Why the hurry?
Did something happen at school?
Um… yeah.
Did you get into trouble
with some delinquents?
- No.
- Don't tell me… a violent teacher?
Um…
You know, Mr. Mori…
Actually, I…
I've fallen in love with someone.
Love? What do you mean?
Yeah, will you listen to me?
I'm late.
Whoa!
I'm sorry.
Oh no!
Are you hurt?
Huh?
Oh, hello.
Oh, I'm sorry!
Three-second rule.
Huh?
What's that cliché
straight out of a girls' manga?
Such a mediocre situation!
A professional manga artist would
reject that storyboard immediately.
Is this… love?
No, just a collision accident.
- You think so?
- Yes!
It's not love.
Geez…
It's not love at all.
But…
It's not love!
Who are you again?
I'm Ranmaru Mori, 450 years old.
Oh my, that's quite a long life.
What's up, Rihito?
You've been grinning for a while now.
That's not true.
So, you found a cute girl at school?
No way!
Now is the time to gather
450 years of wisdom.
Teenage boys.
When parents find out about their crush.
They'll lose interest.
Virgin loss prevention.
Absolutely prevent it.
Rihito has fallen in love.
Hey… Mr. Mori.
I told you to keep it a secret.
Huh? Was that so?
I thought the Tatsuno family
had no secrets and got along well.
I'm sorry.
"Sorry" isn't enough!
He is right! Our family rule
has always been no secrets.
Right? Grandpa.
So, what kind of girl is she?
I'll check if you're being
deceived by a bad girl.
That's absolutely not true.
She's a kind and cute girl.
You don't get it.
Those are the ones
you need to watch out for.
As expected of the third generation,
you understand.
Where did you meet her?
On the way to the ceremony.
They bumped into each other
at a corner and fell in love.
Why did you tell them?
I see. Rihito, you're so simple-minded.
That's not true.
I've never felt this way before.
I see.
As your senior in life,
let me give you one piece of advice.
What?
Make sure you use protection.
Right? Grandpa.
Hmm.
You bastard.
That's not right.
Bastard?
Rihito is only 15 years old.
Condoms? Are you serious?
That's not the issue here.
Giving in to pleasure with heightened
emotions is absolutely unacceptable.
Preposterous.
Shouldn't you teach that as a parent?
I'm sorry, you're right.
Stop it.
Everyone's making fun of me.
Rihito, I never intended to.
I was stupid to ask Mr. Mori for advice.
Oh dear, you've upset a teenage boy.
VIRGIN LOSS PREVENTION
ABSOLUTELY PREVENT IT
I messed up.
Rihito, I'm sorry.
I was just too worried and overstepped.
It's fine. I understand.
No, I can't leave things like this.
To make it up to you,
I'll do anything you want.
Really?
Actually, I wanted to ask for your advice.
Anything you want.
How should I approach Aoi
next time I see her?
Rihito, I need to confirm one thing.
What?
Love doesn't always work out
the way we want.
When you lose someone,
you'll experience great sadness.
Are you speaking from your own experience?
Yes.
Ranmaru.
It seems the promised time has come.
I wanted to live
with Lord Nobunaga much longer.
This Nobunaga,
has no regrets.
Are you sure?
I have no choice.
Lord Nobunaga.
I'll never love someone again.
My love stories never work out.
Don't say that.
Don't worry about it.
This is my destiny.
Well, basically…
Love is, more or less…
It comes with sadness and pain.
Do you still like that girl, Rihito?
Not that deeply.
- But…
- But?
I want to like her that much.
I see.
You know what? Actually.
This is the handkerchief she lent me
when we bumped into each other.
What is it?
I haven't returned it yet.
I sleep with it under my pillow.
Why?
I hope to see her in my dreams.
Too cute.
Is this kind of creepy?
No, not at all. You're not a creep.
- You think so?
- Yes.
Rihito, may I borrow that?
Sure, but why?
Hey, pervert.
Pervert.
What are you sniffing?
I apologize.
Seriously.
That handkerchief…
You might never return it.
I must stop this first love.
Sniff, sniff.
Hey!
This is definitely the right room.
Shh! Shh…
Be quiet!
I am a vampire.
I'm not a pervert, so please don't worry.
What?
Vampire.
A real one?
Yes.
You must be so scared.
Is that why you're here?
Vampires can't enter a house
unless invited by the residents.
Yes.
This girl gets it.
Wait, I shouldn't be impressed.
Now is the time to gather
450 years of wisdom.
Teenage girls are
easily embarrassed
when their feelings are pointed out…
Embarrassed.
- Deflated.
- Go!
- Yeah!
You're in love, aren't you?
Huh?
No, I'm not.
Yes, you definitely are.
Your face says you are.
Is this girl trying to play dumb?
I won't allow it.
I'm reading your mind right now.
- What?
- This morning, on your way to school.
You bumped into someone.
Ah… yes!
You fell in love with that boy, right?
No, not at all.
She's quite stubborn.
That's not true.
You had a romantic encounter
with a wonderful boy.
Is there anyone
who doesn't fall in love? No!
A wonderful boy?
He's a wonderful boy, right?
- He was a kind person.
- Right.
That's all.
Could she actually be an idiot?
Um…
You don't understand anything.
Huh?
Pure smile, beautiful glass-like eyes,
soft-looking lips.
Adorable bed hair.
How could you not fall in love?!
Why? Why doesn't she get it?!
Why? Why?
I don't have time for love right now.
What do you mean "no time"?
I enjoy hanging out with friends
and starting club activities too.
Plus, my parents keep nagging me to study.
And I need time for my hobbies too.
What are you saying?
Time is what you make of it.
You are now,
in the precious prime of your youth.
Youth is fleeting.
Fall in love, young lady.
Ah, no, um…
I'm not recommending love, but…
- Um…
- Aoi! Are you still awake?
Go to bed now.
Huh?
Mr. Vampire?
His appearance, the way he talks…
He was exactly like the vampire
I've admired since childhood.
I came to stop love,
but ended up encouraging it.
Silly fool.
I'm off.
- Hello there!
- Hello.
Damn sun.
Thank you for this.
Maybe next time.
Together… No! That's too casual.
Damn!
Today I'll just thank her
and return the handkerchief.
But maybe we could at least
exchange LINE contacts…
Ah… What should I do?
He's too cute.
Good morning, Rihito.
Oh, good morning, Aoi.
Ah, um…
Here…
Thank you for the handkerchief.
You washed it?
Yes, my thanks to you.
Thank you.
- Shall we go?
- Yeah.
That girl is quite the schemer.
Flirting with my Rihito.
Ouch! Hot, hot! Burning hot.
Ouch!
No bread in your mouth today?
I'm not holding any today.
Oh, Rihito.
Mr. Mori.
Mori?
Mr. Mori!
KOINOBA HOT SPRINGS
Ouch, sunburn…
Mr. Mori.
Oh, there you are.
What is it? Rihito.
Look at this.
I exchanged LINE contacts with Aoi.
What? LINE?
In other words, secret messages.
Huh? Yeah.
We became friends!
Friends?
So what should I send as my first message?
I need your advice.
- Please.
- Welcome.
Wow…
Aoi?
Huh?
Rihito, why are you here?
This is my house.
I see.
It's my first time here.
It's retro and lovely.
We've been running it for 60 years.
Wow, amazing!
I'm looking forward to the bath.
Are you here by chance?
Our bath at home broke down.
Mr. Vampire?
Huh?
You're Mr. Vampire
who visited me yesterday, right?
I'm thrilled to see you again so soon.
You work here?
Mr. Mori, what's going on?
Well, um…
This is…
My biggest crisis
since the Honnō-ji Incident.
Lord Nobunaga!
Calm down, Ranmaru.
There must be a way.
Yes.
It was a dream. You were dreaming.
Amazing. Whoa!
What a dreamy girl.
A dream?
Is that so?
But about that vampire,
was it really me?
Um…
Do you have any proof
that it was definitely me in reality?
Now that you mention it…
Your hair was standing up.
My hair is down right now though.
Your eyes were kind of slanted too.
My eyes are quite droopy.
- You're right.
- See?
It was just a dream. A dream.
Is that so?
But I rarely dream, so I wonder…
Welcome!
Please relax.
Oh… okay.
Please…
I'll be leaving too.
Rihito.
Mr. Vampire
Wait.
Huh?
I knew it. You are Mr. Vampire.
But why just now--
That makes sense.
It's difficult to live
as a vampire in this world.
So that's why you're living in disguise.
I also pretend not to know in public.
- Huh?
- Um…
I think I've fallen in love, after all.
She's in love with Rihito, after all.
With Mr. Vampire.
In that case,
Last resort.
Could it be… Mr. Vampire likes me too?
I have no choice
but to devour her in one go!
Mr. Mori?
Rihito.
Mr. Mori.
Who are you trying to kiss?
Huh?
It's a misunderstanding.
I'm not trying to kiss anyone.
I was trying to suck her blood.
- Mr. Mori.
- No, it's a misunderstanding.
A bug, there was a bug. Right here.
Huh?
I was killing it.
- I see.
- Yes.
- Yes!
What were you planning to do
if we hadn't been interrupted?
Mr. Vampire.
Then I'll be going now.
Yeah, take care.
I was so close.
I won't let you escape next time.
Mr. Mori.
You have special feelings
for Aoi, don't you?
So he noticedmy murderous intent…
You're in love with her, right?
Huh?
You were sniffing Aoi's handkerchief.
If I hadn't come, you would've kissed…
No, absolutely not.
Even today,
you dressed up nicely for Aoi, right?
No, this isn't dressing up or anything.
Mr. Mori.
We're love rivals now.
He's so off the mark.
It's actually adorable.
Alright.
I won't lose.
Huh?
You're so innocent.
I won't lose to you, Mr. Mori.
Late, so late.
Wow, it's curry! Looks delicious!
Let's eat.
Yeah, this is it.
How can you eat so calmly?
Rihito isn't home yet.
Who's Rihito again?
Just reading magazines
at the convenience store.
He better not be doing
something inappropriate.
He misunderstood that I,
whom he greatly trusts,
like the same girl.
He must be suspicious.
Ran-chan, just sit down, okay?
He might lose trust in people
and turn to delinquency.
He might start stealing bikes.
He might start breaking windows at school.
- Ozaki Yutaka lyrics.
- He might start smoking!
If his pure blood
gets contaminated with nicotine.
It's like pouring toilet water
into Romanée-Conti.
What are you muttering about?
Third generation owner,
where do delinquent boys hang out?
- Huh?
- You. Tell me now.
Yes.
This is the third case since last month.
Police are investigating
a possible connection between these cases.
In both of the bodies found so far,
there were bite-like marks
found near the neck.
The autopsy results are awaited.
It's dangerous these days.
Buddha have mercy.
Right next to the entertainment district
lined with hotels.
Rihito, Rihito.
There are no credible eyewitness accounts.
Police…
Who am I? Who am I? Who am I?
Franken the senior
My name is Franken
Ready to fight, muscles roaring
Day and night,
I'm all about muscle training
Our leader
I believe in muscles, muscles
Muscles never betray you
With a healthy body and soul
I crush my enemies
Our leader
Muscle-head boss! Muscle-head boss!
Muscle-head boss!
Franken the senior
Muscle-head boss! Muscle-head boss!
Muscle-head boss!
Franken the senior
Muscle-head boss! Muscle-head boss!
Muscle-head boss!
Franken the senior
My name is Franken
I don't smoke, I'm a non-smoker boss
Why put nicotine in your body?
I believe in muscles, muscles
Muscles are my everything
Fighting is just another muscle workout
Our leader
Who am I? Who am I? Who am I?
Franken the senior
Let's kick it up a notch.
Yeah.
Have you seen Rihito?
Rihito?
Who are you?
Is Rihito here?
So what's your deal?
Rihito! It's me, Ranmaru.
Who are you? Come on!
Rihito.
I'm looking for Rihito.
What the hell?
You've been messing with my junior.
Your blood.
What color is it?
This scent… could it be?
This guy…
That's quite the virgin we have here.
- Holy crap…
- Let's get out of here.
Damn it.
I trusted those guys.
No, your purity
is wonderful just as it is.
Huh?
Wait, bro.
No one's ever said that to me before.
Well, thank you. Goodbye then.
I'm in love!
I'll follow you forever, bro!
Huh?
Mr. Mori?
Rihito.
Where have you been? I was worried!
Oh, I just needed to buy something.
Don't tell me, cigarettes?
HOW TO WIN AGAINST A ROMANTIC RIVAL
Could a rival be…
me?
Yeah.
Give it back.
Bro, who is this kid?
Shut up, you pest.
Pest?
Who are you?
Ken Shinozuka, a senior at Rugoshi High.
Nickname is "Franken."
Only "Ken" is matched.
So you're a senior.
Yeah!
Oh, right… Franken.
Ouch…
I need to keep bad influences away
from Rihito at school.
Could you watch over him?
Got it. Leave it to me.
It's fine, Mr. Mori.
You don't need to ask him.
I was worried because
I couldn't watch over you during the day.
I'm not a child anymore.
That's exactly why I'm worried.
I'm counting on you.
I'll step it up!
Ah, it feels good.
It's been a while
since I could stretch my legs.
Bro, it's the best.
I have an elder brother
but no beefy little brother like you.
Mr. Mori, you have a brother?
Yes.
What kind of person is he?
Does he look like you?
Whoa, bro! You can work out here too.
Stop that.
Whoa! I'll do it.
- Don't.
- Let's kick it up a notch!
- Stop it.
- Yo!
Who are you again?
I'm Franken.
Franken?
A vampire and Frankenstein.
A monster has come for me.
Granny. I'm coming to join you soon.
Oh Buddha, save me. Oh Buddha, save me.
- Can I stay over tonight?
- Absolutely not.
Sounds fun.
I'll sleep in your room too.
Let's have a pillow fight.
Nice.
So that means…
virgins in both hands?
KOINOBA HOT SPRINGS
Franken is so disciplined.
Yeah, working out never betrays you.
You should work out too, Rihito.
Maybe I should try it too.
But bro really can't handle mornings, huh?
I tried so hard to wake him up,
but he didn't budge at all.
Vampires can't handle sunlight.
Vamp?
It's his vampire persona.
Brother?
Oh, Aoi.
What? Aoi is Franken's sister?
Oh, yeah.
You two look nothing alike.
I hear that a lot.
Huh?
Brother, yesterday, that vamp--
Wait… You stayed at Mr. Mori's house?
Yeah, it was awesome.
Not fair.
Hey Rihito, can I come visit too?
- Of course.
- Yay!
I can meet Mr. Vampire.
What? Aoi?
You know about Mr. Mori's vampire persona?
You just said "vampire," didn't you?
Huh? I didn't say anything like that.
I see. I must have misheard.
That's right.
You guys.
Weren't you just talking about vampires?
Hey!
Who are you?
This is our homeroom teacher,
Mr. Sakamoto.
Did you just say, "Mr. Mori, the vampire"?
There's a guy named Mori
who lives and works at our place.
He often talks about being a vampire.
I see…
Could you tell me more about it?
For example,
"I've been alive for 450 years," and such.
He was favored by Oda Nobunaga.
What?
Wow.
Ran Mori…
I'm Umetaro Sakamoto, with completely
Different faces by day and night
By day, a kind high school teacher
Beloved Mr. Sakamoto
But at night, I'm someone else
My real job is Vampire Hunter
Vampires killed our ancestors
Descendants gathered together
Banbanbanbanbanban Vampire Hunter
Vampires are the target
We gathered to take revenge
Banbanbanbanbanban Vampire Hunter
Vampire Hunter
My ancestor Ryoma Sakamoto
Was killed by vampire Ranmaru Mori
Ten years ago, I let him slip away
Swallowing my tears that day
Never forget my clan's sworn enemy
Vampire Ranmaru Mori
Vampires to be exterminated
Bang bang, shoot them with my gun
Banbanbanbanbanban Vampire Hunter
Huh?
Ah… Oh, it's nothing.
Sorry! Please, go ahead.
Banbanbanbanbanban Vampire Hunter
Vampire Hunter
Ryoma Sakamoto was
originally from Tosa Domain.
Three years as a teacher, moving around
Until I finally found Ranmaru Mori
I finally found Ranmaru Mori
The time has come to fulfill my desire
Teacher, who killed Ryoma Sakamoto?
RYOMA
The Shinsengumi, right?
It was the Mimawarigumi.
To avenge my clan's grudge, that's
What it means to be a Vampire Hunter
There are various theories.
Banbanbanbanbanban Vampire Hunter
Vampire Hunter
I've been waiting for this day, Ran Mori.
Stop that gun.
Why?
This bathhouse
has been around for 60 years.
Damaging its pristine condition
would be a sin.
You've changed, Ran Mori.
You used to kill indiscriminately.
What's wrong?
Have you grown attached to humans?
Impossible.
Who is stronger, one who fights for others
or one who fights for himself?
Which do you think is stronger?
The one who fights for others.
Take this.
Obviously the one who fights for himself.
Shut up.
Too bad for you, Sakamoto.
The ones to be exterminated are…
the Sakamoto clan.
I've been waiting for this moment,
Ran Mori.
Let go.
Suck my blood.
What?
- Suck my blood.
- What?
Ten years ago, when I first found you,
I couldn't move at all.
It's because of the act of drinking blood.
I thought it was
the most beautiful thing in this world.
That's when I realized.
My life is not meant for killing you.
My life was meant
for you to suck my blood.
Huh?
Now.
No, don't say, "Now."
My blood is delicious.
What's with that confidence?
Virgin blood is pure
and incredibly delicious, right?
- Yes.
- I'm 100% virgin.
Ran Mori!
I've kept my pure blood just for you.
Come on.
Drink your fill.
It's blood for you.
Ran Mori, wait.
Stop it, Ran Mori.
- Huh?
- I'm kind of… full now.
Why? Why won't you drink?
Look! Wide open. Wide open.
It's wide open. Drink my blood.
I'm not thirsty,
and I'm not really hungry either.
Liar.
I've never had someone
come on me so aggressively…
When you beg me to drink,
it's kind of a turn-off.
Fine, I get it.
Don't you dare drink it.
- Fine, I won't.
- Drink it.
Come on, you should drink it.
You're a vampire, aren't you?
Look! See.
I'm sorry.
I'll never give up on Ran Mori.
KOINOBA HOT SPRINGS
I want to dive straight in
Into your towering clouds
That might disappear
The end is not yet here
Don't bother coming
Forever
Water, blood? Water, blood? Water, blood?
Which one do you like? Like?
La La La La La La Like?
Bon appétit
Water, blood? Water, blood? Water, blood?
Which one do you like? Like?
La La La La La La Like?
Bon appétit
Stop time right now, here in my arms
Your dress that's gotten a bit shorter
I cherish you
Your innocent tail swaying unknowingly
By someone's dirty hands
So you won't be snatched away
I'll protect you
You've stolen my heart
I can't steal you
Thought I had
Found true strength all along
Oh, what am I to you?
I want to dive straight in
Into your towering clouds
That might disappear
Even if I'm reborn,
I'll still choose only you
I'll find you, so don't worry
Oh, how many more nights?
Summer festival? Summer festival
With your tanned skin
It's so sinful
I love everything about you
Gimme your okay, okay
Okay? Alright!
From love at first sight to bite
You're still too young for this
I wanna take a day off
Just one bite is okay, okay
I got to spend the entire summer vacation
with Rihito.
Ranmaru is happy.
Which one do you like? Like?
La La La La La La Like?
Bon appétit…
SUMMER FESTIVAL
Rihito! I've kept you waiting.
Say cheese!
Bro. Let's go to the festival.
Rihito?
I thought it'd be fun with everyone.
I'm excited for the festival.
Yo! Ran Mori.
Why are you here too?
Mr. Sakamoto is our homeroom teacher.
Huh?
You're close with Mr. Mori?
What a coincidence.
We're not close at all.
Why are you being so cold?
Hey, don't touch my bro like that.
Why?
Ask for permission.
Whose permission?
I have Ran Mori's permission.
You don't have it.
You see?
A chance to get closer to Aoi.
A perfect chance
to get closer to Mr. Vampire.
This girl is dangerous.
The relationship of Ran Mori and Rihito.
I'll completely sabotage this.
Bro. Hey, bro!
I've got a great idea.
Hmm…
Let's get Rihito
and my sister Aoi together.
Huh?
Then no bad guys will go after Rihito.
Great idea. Leave it to me.
The worst bug is your own sister.
This means…
SIBLINGS
Ran Mori wants to drink Rihito's blood.
Rihito likes Aoi.
Aoi and Franken are siblings.
Franken is trying to get
Rihito and Aoi together.
If those two start dating…
Ran Mori will be devastated.
This means…
my chance has come.
Hey, Mr. Mori.
I think today is my chance.
What chance?
If you get close with Aoi…
I might just confess my feelings…
Confess my feelings?
Con-fe-ssion
DON'T CONFESS
Confession means…
losing his virginity.
Crisis.
Crisis!
DON'T CONFESS, CONFESSION MEANS
LOSING HIS VIRGINITY, CRISIS!
Oh! Mr. Vampire.
Oh. A candy store.
What's this? What's this?
- This is a shooting gallery.
- Shooting gallery?
WATER BALLOON FISHING
What's this? Look, look!
Rihito, that would look good on you.
- Would it suit me?
- Try it on.
- How is it?
- Cute! It suits you.
Is it moving?
Wow.
Wow!
I'll take three, please.
- Let's do this.
- Alright.
That's amazing.
- Wow!
- You're a genius, Rihito.
Right, Franken?
What color is your blood?
Goldfish… blood color…
But you're really amazing, Rihito.
You think so?
An unexpected mutual attraction flag.
This is the road to losing virginity!
Full speed ahead!
That's incredible.
This girl, I can't let my guard down.
Oh! Mr. Vampire is looking at me!
Alright. I'll confess my feelings today.
Must prevent Rihito's confession.
Just one more, please.
Where's Ran Mori?
My bro is right next to me…
He's gone!
Bro?
Mr. Mori.
Mr. Vampire.
Would you like to talk for a bit?
Yes.
Excuse me.
How's this? Must be scared, little girl?
Amazing.
I've never experienced this before.
I'll make this summer festival
a traumatic memory for her.
How romantic.
Now, let the hell begin.
What a wonderful night, Mr. Vampire.
Beautiful.
I knew it. Mr. Vampire also likes me.
Now, what should I do?
I could devour her right here, but…
Mr. Vampire.
Yes?
Mr. Vampire, are you in love?
I don't have feelings like love.
However,
There is someone I must have.
But I cannot fulfill that desire yet.
I need more time.
Wait… wait a second!
Is it because I'm still
a high school student? A child?
When will your desire be fulfilled?
In three years.
Bingo!
So in three years, when I turn 18,
that's what you mean, right?
I never knew you cared about me so much.
So, Aoi, are you in love?
Yes.
How dare she say that so brazenly?
I really want to throw myself
into your arms right now.
But if Mr. Vampire is holding back,
I must hold back too.
He seems so close,
I could almost reach out and touch.
But seems so far away.
This is a battle I absolutely cannot lose.
Aoi.
In three years, I'll give you all of me.
Mr. Vampire.
Ran Mori.
Aoi.
Shall we go?
Oh, yes.
Aoi.
Oh! Aoi, Mr. Mori.
Oh, Rihito.
Where were you two going?
Huh?
We just met over there.
Yes, I got separated
and was wandering around.
Oh, I see.
What color is your blood?!
- Winner!
- He did it!
Thanks.
Brother?
Franken. Franken.
Aoi. I won.
What are you doing? Come down quickly.
Trophy.
It's obvious.
I won this arm wrestling match trophy!
The end of a festival means
sparklers for two, right?
You remembered.
Of course.
Rihito, I'm happy about your feelings.
Hey, what do you like, Mr. Mori?
Huh?
I've realized something recently.
I don't have anything special.
I'm not good at studying or sports.
I don't have any hobbies
or things I'm passionate about.
I'm such a boring guy.
Rihito.
Don't rush.
You're still so incredibly young.
As you grow older,
you'll surely find someone
or something you love.
If you have just one thing you love,
you can surely live a happy life.
I see.
Then I already have one.
I already have someone I love.
My sweet fool!
Thank you.
I see.
- It's okay.
- Wait…
You are choking me, Mr. Mori.
Rihito.
Today, just after 8 p.m.,
at a park in Shinjuku, Tokyo,
a report came in about a woman
who had collapsed.
The woman was found with all the blood
drained from her body.
She was taken to the hospital,
but was pronounced dead shortly after.
This is the sixth case of a body
found drained of blood.
Police are investigating a possible
connection with cases from April.
Start working now?
Why are you living in the apartment
behind Koino-yu?
I moved here during summer vacation.
Now we're neighbors, Ran Mori.
Don't ignore me.
Look.
I ranked third among
Vampire Hunters in Japan.
What?
Impressive, right?
VAMPIRE HUNTER RANKING
Look at this!
- You're in the way.
- Oh, I'm sorry.
But you're interesting.
Even though you have
a clear purpose with Rihito.
Helping humans like this.
What's so interesting?
All the vampires I've encountered
were living dissolute and chaotic lives.
When you obtain an immortal body,
at first, you feel invincible
and corrupt yourself.
But after about 100 years, you realize.
This is a hell where you can never die.
By the way,
Sakamoto, do you want eternal life?
I'm not sure about that.
I'd become human again right now
if I could.
I just want to live
an ordinary life earnestly.
And I want to go to eternal sleep
with gratitude.
Such an obvious thing.
Only humans
who feel death nearby can do this.
The reason I work.
Maybe it's because I want to
experience that human-like feeling.
So that the darkness of eternal life
won't swallow me up.
What's going on?
You're a vampire hunter, aren't you?
Vampire hunter?
Do you know Ranmaru Mori?
Did you know that there are
200 different colors of blood?
Goodbye.
Mr. Mori.
Rihito.
What's going on?
Huh?
Earlier, I was showing Aoi
the festival photos.
Rihito, could you send me this photo?
Oh… sure.
Mr. Mori.
So you do like Aoi after all.
What? No, that's not it.
Forget it.
I did talk with Aoi a little bit.
Then why didn't you tell me?
Because you feel guilty about it?
Rihito, you're wrong.
I can't believe you, Mr. Mori.
I thought we agreed to fight fair
if we were rivals?
But Mr. Mori, that's not it.
You said you'd help us.
Yet you're sneaking around behind my back.
Rihito, you're wrong. Please listen.
Besides,
Aoi also likes Mr. Mori.
That's not true.
Aoi likes you.
Don't mock me.
Are you enjoying this?
Making fun of me.
That's not true.
That's not possible!
I trusted you, Mr. Mori.
Just leave me alone. You're bothering me.
Rihito…
- Goodbye, teacher.
- Yes, goodbye.
Oh, teacher.
Oh, Franken.
I had fun the other day.
It was a great summer memory for me too.
Do you still have class?
The night school teacher is sick,
so I'm substituting today.
Night school?
Wow, you're a hard worker.
I'm going all out from now on.
Yeah, good luck.
You too.
Yes.
Alright, let's go, everyone.
Oh, What's wrong? What happened?
- Wait a minute. Are you okay?
- Run!
- What's wrong? What?
- Everyone! What's going on?
- Go!
What are you doing?
You must be Sakamoto?
VAMPIRE HUNTER
THIRD PLACE
So you've been killing hunters
one after another.
So it was you.
Hmm, you really do look alike.
Your ancestor put up quite a fight.
I'm the one who killed Ryoma Sakamoto.
Damn it.
If you're a hunter,
do you know Ranmaru Mori?
Ranmaru Mori… from history?
I have no business with you.
Damn it.
Hmm…
Ran Mori.
Huh?
I'm not excited at all.
After longing for it so much,
the act of sucking blood.
Now I know. So it's not just anyone.
Vampires have hearing
ten times better than humans.
Damn you, Sakamoto.
Damn it!
Nagayoshi Mori, Nagayoshi, Nagayoshi
A vampire for over 450 years
Ruthless and cruel, slaughtering people
Known as "Demon Musashi," feared by all
His helmet adorned with a dragon,
His spear showing no mercy to humans
Devoted to Lord Nobunaga
Well done.
I vowed to stay
- By his side and protect him forever
- Good job.
Until that moment
Raise your face.
It's my brother, Ranmaru.
Oh…
Ranmaru.
Everything changed that day
Everything was taken from me
How could it be
My brother Ranmaru
Ranmaru, I'll never forgive
Never forgive, never forgive
Why did Lord Nobunaga choose Ranmaru?
Why didn't Lord Nobunaga choose me?
Why did you let Lord Nobunaga die?
Why couldn't you protect Lord Nobunaga?
Why, why, why, why, why, why, why, why?
That day I swore revenge on Ranmaru
Ranmaru, I'll never forgive
Never forgive, never forgive
Ranmaru!
Run!
Dammit!
Rihito hates me now.
Rihito.
Rihito?!
INCOMING CALL
UMETARO SAKAMOTO
Yes.
Ran?
That voice.
I'm sorry, Ran Mori.
It's been a while.
Brother Nagayoshi.
Come here right now, Ran.
Rihito.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
No, I should apologize
for the sudden call.
What did you want to talk about?
Hey, Aoi. About Mr. Mori.
Oh, Mr. Mori.
What? Really?
Yes, it was definitely Mr. Mori!
What? Wait, Aoi!
Isn't that direction of the school?
Mr. Mori would never go to school.
Mr. Sakamoto?!
Mr. Sakamoto!
Mr. Sakamoto! Are you okay?
What happened?
Ran Mori is…
So you've come, Ran.
You haven't changed, Brother Nagayoshi.
I never thought I'd see you again.
This is no place for you, brother.
Would you please leave now?
Don't be ridiculous.
After taking what was precious to me,
how dare you act so nonchalant?
Why did you let Lord Nobunaga die?
I entrusted him to you. Why?
It was Lord Nobunaga's destiny.
Why didn't you make Lord Nobunaga
a vampire and give him eternal life?
I could never turn
someone I admire into a vampire.
But nothing is as ugly as death.
Humans are beautiful
because they eventually die.
Since I lost Lord Nobunaga,
I don't know what I'm living for anymore.
Why don't you fight back?
Is it because we're blood brothers?
That's nonsense.
I'll take everything you hold dear.
Mr. Mori.
You're doing well, Ran.
I'm finally ready to fight you.
Don't make me laugh.
Mr. Mori.
Is that all you've got, Ran?
I'll take what's precious to you.
Mr. Mori.
Mr. Mori is alive.
Mr. Mori, Mr. Mori, Mr. Mori.
Mr. Mori.
Mr. Mori!
Hey, Mr. Mori.
Mr. Mori.
I trusted you, Mr. Mori.
Mr. Mori, Mr. Mori!
Mr. Mori!
Mr. Mori.
Rihito.
Who are you, boy?
I'm fine.
You're not okay.
Let's go.
Are you okay?
Hmm.
Rihito, leave me here and run away.
I'll protect you, Mr. Mori.
He's not human.
I see now.
Is this boy your precious one?
You did this to Mr. Mori.
Rihito.
Rihito, Are you okay?
Stop it.
Someone!
I said I'd take everything you hold dear.
How did you do that?
It seems. I did it.
I never knew I had such power.
But this is where it ends.
Farewell, Ran.
Take this!
Rihito, that won't work.
No…
What?
Is the cross working?
It's super-effective.
Yes.
I can't believe it.
- Why are you afraid of crosses?
- Wait, stay back.
I'm sorry. Excuse me.
I'm completely fine.
Haven't you seen it? That forbidden book.
What "forbidden book"?
Wikipedia.
Wikipedia?
VAMPIRES ARE WEAK AGAINST CROSSES,
GARLIC, SUNLIGHT AND HOLY WATER.
It was written there.
Weak against crosses and garlic.
Ever since I saw that.
You were brainwashed by Wikipedia.
- Take that!
- How persistent!
Mr. Mori, are you okay?
Yes, I am.
Rihito, how about you?
Blood.
I'm fine. This is nothing.
You came to help me.
But in the end, I couldn't do anything.
The cross was Aoi's idea.
Rihito.
Thank you for protecting me.
Before I realized,
you've become so brave and strong.
I was just desperate.
I'm so fortunate.
Mr. Mori.
I'm sorry.
Huh?
I said such terrible things.
I should be the one apologizing.
I'm sorry for keeping secrets from you.
Come on, come on.
Mr. Sakamoto. Are you okay?
Are you okay, Mr. Sakamoto?
- Can you stand up?
- I'll help.
Here we go.
- Watch your step.
- Okay.
- Slowly…
- Ran Mori.
- Ran Mori?
- Where's Ran Mori?
- Mr. Mori?
- He's fine.
He's okay.
Let's go. This way.
What is it?
You always get all the precious things.
It's not fair.
What?
Everyone adores you.
Lord Nobunaga too.
Father and Mother too.
I've always been alone.
Brother.
This is the first time
I've heard your true feelings.
It seems I now have a weapon
that you don't possess, brother.
A weapon?
People call it…
They call it "love."
I've always been…
I thought those who fought for
their own desires were the strongest.
But today,
I displayed the greatest power
I've had in 450 years.
Because I wanted to protect
someone precious.
It's okay.
If Ran Mori is safe, then it's all good.
Be careful.
From now on,
you'll live close to me, brother.
What?
Now that I know your weakness,
if handled correctly,
you're actually the weakest.
You want me to suffer a living hell?
No.
I want you to live and find love again.
Impossible.
It can be a human or something else.
Like an idol, a pet,
or a character from a game or anime.
It could be a car or a train.
Anything you love is fine.
In this era, we call that…
A "fave," they call it.
Fave?
When you find your "fave,"
every day begins to shine.
You'll look forward to tomorrow.
Your life will start moving again.
That's…
even for a vampire?
Yes, even for a vampire.
Happy birthday to you
I'm filming this.
Happy birthday, dear Rihito
Rihito!
Happy birthday to you
Blow them out.
- Congratulations!
Rihito is finally 16 years old.
Are you that excited about him
turning 18 in two years, Ran Mori?
You never change.
Rihito.
Congratulations!
Thank you!
Oh, that's cool!
Right?
It'll be useful in emergencies.
A cross.
Sorry.
From me.
What?!
What is it?
Nagayoshi, are you into Heisei era gals?
It's like Lord Nobunaga's mindset.
Huh? How so?
Brother, you finally found your "fave"?
No, I haven't decided yet.
So outdated.
Pushing your fave
onto others too much is questionable.
- What did you say, ugly girl!?
- What?
- Hey, Don't insult my sister.
- You muscle-head.
- Muscle-head?
- Thanks.
Why are you happy, brother?
I'm the Muscle-head boss!
- Rihito, this is from me.
- From me to my 16-year-old son.
You bastard. What are you thinking?
Forcing your son into sexual elation
is clearly harassment.
That's outrageous.
I'm sorry.
Honestly!
What's this? "0.01"
Brother, stop it.
- A mechanical pencil?
- Just be quiet.
- It's a keychain.
- Keychain?
- Let me see that.
- I've never seen this before.
By the way, Ran-san.
You must not drink Rihito's blood.
How did you reveal my ambition?
It's the wisdom of age.
If you really need to drink blood,
you should drink my blood instead.
Oh, no, that's quite all right.
I prefer the blood of 18-year-old virgins.
What?!
I'm also a virgin. Forever 18.
No, that's wrong.
Mr. Mori.
Your character is so consistent.
Vampire persona, right?
Yeah.
Virgin loss prevention at all costs.
Absolutely prevent it.
Only two more years until Rihito turns 18.
Just two more years.
Two more years.
Babanba Banbanban
Babanba Banban vampire
What a nice bath, Bababan
Somehow I'm working at a public bath
Vampire Bababan Vampire Bababan
This is Koino-yu Bath that I love you
Babanba Banbanban
Babanba Banban vampire
Looking young, seriously unserious
Sleep in bed till sunset
Battle on the steamy stage
Nothing goes his way, a vampire
This seems like a comedy
Something we can laugh off
This family keeps me warm today too
Too many obstacles in my way
To suck your blood
I became overprotective
And became love's enemy
What a nice bath, Bababan
Family bathhouse, that's what I long for
Humans are Bababan
Wonderful Bababan
Now a vampire, once a human
Babanba Banbanban
Babanba Banban vampire
What a nice bath, Bababan
Even on days of fights
Even on lonely nights
Wash it away, Bababan
Laugh it off, Bababan
This is koino-yu
Come and take a bath anytime
Babanba Banbanban
Babanba Banban vampire
FESTIVAL
ENTRANCE CEREMONY
Mr. Mori.